A Guide to the Virginia Chapter of the National Organization for Women Records, 1971-2004, 2011
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Newsletters and local chapter files, 1973-2004. (Box 13-19)
  - Virginia NOW newsletter, Virginia NOW Choices (oversize), 1989-1991. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Virginia NOW newsletter, Virginia NOW Choices (oversize), 1992. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Virginia NOW newsletter, Virginia NOW Choices (oversize), 1993-1996. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Virginia NOW newsletter, Virginia NOW Choices (oversize), 1997-2003. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Action newsletters, etc., 1981-1983. (Box 19, Folder 15-16)
  - NOW newsletters from other states, 1991. (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Tech chapter, 1983. (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Winchester-Frederick County chapter, 1982. (Box 19, Folder 19)